const questions = {
    "week-1": [
        {
    
          question: "Wilhelm Wundt and his students used a technique known as _________ to study mental states.",
    
          options: ["behaviorism", "intensity measurement", "componentialism", "introspection"],
    
          answer: "introspection"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "Which psychologist extensively tested his own memory to develop theories of cognition?",
    
          options: ["Aristotle", "Wundt", "Ebbinghaus", "Chomsky"],
    
          answer: "Ebbinghaus"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "All connectionist models share the assumption that:",
    
          options: [
    
            "a central processor directs the flow of information",
    
            "processing occurs in parallel",
    
            "knowledge is stored in various storehouses",
    
            "processing occurs serially"
    
          ],
    
          answer: "processing occurs in parallel"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "The term “limited capacity processors” suggests that:",
    
          options: [
    
            "computers have limited memory storage",
    
            "neurons can only fire at a certain rate",
    
            "human beings can only do so many things at once",
    
            "processing in the brain occurs in parallel"
    
          ],
    
          answer: "human beings can only do so many things at once"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "A traditional “school” within psychology that had as its goal the identification of the simplest possible units of the mind:",
    
          options: ["functionalism", "structuralism", "behaviorism", "componentialism"],
    
          answer: "structuralism"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "Cognitive psychology is broad, and thus overlaps with many other fields including neuroscience, philosophy, and ______.",
    
          options: ["botany", "astronomy", "linguistics", "mining"],
    
          answer: "linguistics"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "William James’s ideas regarding psychological phenomena centered around the idea of",
    
          options: [
    
            "the sea of the subconscious",
    
            "a stream of consciousness",
    
            "a stream of subconsciousness",
    
            "a sea of consciousness"
    
          ],
    
          answer: "a stream of consciousness"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "A body of knowledge structured according to what its proponents consider important, which guides research topics and research methods, is called a ___________.",
    
          options: ["hypothesis", "methodology", "paradigm", "metaphor"],
    
          answer: "paradigm"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "The analysis of information processing systems is of special interest to _____ psychology.",
    
          options: ["behavioral", "biological", "psychoanalytic", "cognitive"],
    
          answer: "cognitive"
    
        },
    
        {
    
          question: "If you think of cognitive processing as a type of information processing, then the brain is the ______ and the cognitive processes themselves are the ______.",
    
          options: [
    
            "response; stimulus",
    
            "hardware; software",
    
            "software; hardware",
    
            "stimulus; response"
    
          ],
    
          answer: "hardware; software"
        }
      ],
    "week-2": [{
        question: "Which of the following processes the sensations coming into each sense organ, allowing us to understand and interpret the sensations we receive?",
        options: ["environment", "sensory system", "stimulus", "brain"],
        answer: "sensory system"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of these psychological approaches focuses on how humans use principles of organization to understand our surroundings?",
        options: ["perception-action", "gestalt", "top-down", "computational"],
        answer: "gestalt"
      },
      {
        question: "The two best studied forms of perception are:",
        options: ["visual and auditory", "visual and olfactory", "visual and haptic", "auditory and olfactory"],
        answer: "visual and auditory"
      },
      {
        question: "Reversible figures illustrate the principle of:",
        options: ["bottom-up processing", "figure-ground organization", "size constancy", "retinal imagery"],
        answer: "figure-ground organization"
      },
      {
        question: "A stencil provides a good analogy for the theory of:",
        options: ["top-down processing", "template matching", "good continuation", "featural analysis"],
        answer: "template matching"
      },
      {
        question: "Gibson’s theory of direct perception is in direct opposition to the ______ approach to perception.",
        options: ["connectionist", "constructivist", "bottom-up", "gestalt"],
        answer: "constructivist"
      },
      {
        question: "Prototype matching theory argues that percepts are compared to ______ in memory.",
        options: ["idealized representations", "abstract dot patterns", "gestalt principles", "lists of features"],
        answer: "idealized representations"
      },
      {
        question: "___________ are to visual perception what phonemes are to language, according to Biederman.",
        options: ["templates", "distal stimuli", "geons", "receptors"],
        answer: "geons"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of these help us estimate objects’ size and distance to aid in our perception?",
        options: ["stimuli", "sensations", "cues", "neurons"],
        answer: "cues"
      },
      {
        question: "You are eating a meal at an open-air restaurant a few hundred yards from the ocean. You hear a constant whooshing sound. According to the likelihood principle, what would you assume caused the noise?",
        options: ["an earthquake", "a series of airplanes landing", "traffic a few miles away", "waves crashing on the beach"],
        answer: "waves crashing on the beach"
      }],
    "week-3": [{
      question: "Noticing a red flower among a field of purple flowers illustrates ______.",
      options: [
        "the attention capture phenomenon",
        "the cocktail party effect",
        "the bottleneck of attention",
        "a shadowing task"
      ],
      answer: "the attention capture phenomenon"
    },
    {
      question: "According to Treisman, if you listen to two competing messages simultaneously, you are more likely to pick up information from the second message if that message ______.",
      options: [
        "relates to the other message",
        "was spoken more slowly",
        "includes a spotlight",
        "is louder"
      ],
      answer: "relates to the other message"
    },
    {
      question: "Stroop interference lessens when:",
      options: [
        "participants are given more practice at naming colors",
        "participants are encouraged to focus carefully",
        "participants are given more practice at reading color names",
        "participants are better readers"
      ],
      answer: "participants are given more practice at naming colors"
    },
    {
      question: "When listening to a conversation, your attention is momentarily diverted when you hear your name spoken in a different conversation across the room. This is an example of the:",
      options: [
        "Stroop effect",
        "cocktail party effect",
        "dichotic listening phenomenon",
        "attenuation effect"
      ],
      answer: "cocktail party effect"
    },
    {
      question: "Broadbent, in proposing his filter theory of attention, argued that an attentional filter lets some information through and blocks out the rest. This filter is based upon:",
      options: [
        "the meaning of the message",
        "a physical characteristic of the message, such as its location",
        "the importance of the message",
        "the number of repetitions of the message"
      ],
      answer: "a physical characteristic of the message, such as its location"
    },
    {
      question: "Our attention has been said to involve a ______ that filters out everything except the information we are attending to.",
      options: ["net", "bottleneck", "switchboard", "bridge"],
      answer: "bottleneck"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these is known to influence the cocktail party effect?",
      options: [
        "a person’s level of extroversion or introversion",
        "a person’s intelligence",
        "the salience of the message",
        "cultural differences in filtering abilities"
      ],
      answer: "the salience of the message"
    },
    {
      question: "According to ____ theory, we never actually acquire unattended material at all.",
      options: ["capacity", "bottleneck", "schema", "attenuation"],
      answer: "schema"
    },
    {
      question: "Children with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD):",
      options: [
        "are more likely to be girls than boys",
        "cannot sustain vigilance on repetitive or dull tasks",
        "cannot switch attention from one task to another",
        "cannot devote mental resources to tasks"
      ],
      answer: "cannot sustain vigilance on repetitive or dull tasks"
    },
    {
      question: "According to Treisman, people tend to process:",
      options: [
        "only as much as is necessary to separate the attended from the unattended message",
        "at the highest possible level given the amount of background distraction",
        "only to the level of linguistic characteristics, separating it into words",
        "only to the level of physical characteristics"
      ],
      answer: "only as much as is necessary to separate the attended from the unattended message"
    }],
    "week-4" : [
        {
          question: "Remembering your phone number in sequences such as xxx-xxx-xxxx and your Social Security number in sequences such as xxx-xx-xxxx are examples of ______.",
          options: [
            "short-term memory",
            "encoding",
            "sensory memory",
            "chunking"
          ],
          answer: "chunking"
        },
        {
          question: "The briefest form of memory is ______ memory.",
          options: [
            "long-term",
            "working",
            "short-term",
            "sensory"
          ],
          answer: "sensory"
        },
        {
          question: "The suffix effect relates to which type of memory?",
          options: [
            "iconic",
            "echoic",
            "short term",
            "long term"
          ],
          answer: "echoic"
        },
        {
          question: "The fact that the size of the memory set does affect search time in short-term memory suggests that:",
          options: [
            "search is both self-terminating and serial",
            "search is a serial process",
            "search is a parallel process",
            "search is exhaustive"
          ],
          answer: "search is a serial process"
        },
        {
          question: "Some experts describe memory as a ______, while others believe it is a ______.",
          options: [
            "checklist; blueprint",
            "secret; journey",
            "structure; process",
            "ball of string; pool of water"
          ],
          answer: "structure; process"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of these is a component of the memory formation process?",
          options: [
            "retrieval",
            "interference",
            "modality",
            "inspiration"
          ],
          answer: "retrieval"
        },
        {
          question: "Unattended information is stored briefly in:",
          options: [
            "sensory memory",
            "short-term memory",
            "long-term memory",
            "secondary memory"
          ],
          answer: "sensory memory"
        },
        {
          question: "In the absence of rehearsal, short-term memory tends to:",
          options: [
            "last about 8 seconds",
            "last about 20 seconds",
            "decay slowly over 24 hours",
            "last for an unlimited amount of time"
          ],
          answer: "last about 20 seconds"
        },
        {
          question: "The concept of fluid intelligence is highly related to:",
          options: [
            "working memory capacity",
            "echoic memory capacity",
            "iconic memory capacity",
            "interference"
          ],
          answer: "working memory capacity"
        },
        {
          question: "One basic physiological mechanism for learning is the ____ rule, which states that if a synapse between two neurons is repeatedly activated at about the same time the postsynaptic neuron fires, the chemistry of the synapse changes.",
          options: [
            "Baddeley",
            "Hebb",
            "Tulving",
            "Carlson"
          ],
          answer: "Hebb"
        }

    ],
    "week-5": [
        {
          question: "Ebbinghaus’s forgetting curve demonstrates that:",
          options: [
            "forgetting is rapid at first and then levels off",
            "forgetting is slow at first and then speeds up",
            "forgetting occurs at a steady pace, beginning immediately after learning",
            "no forgetting occurs until 24 hours after learning"
          ],
          answer: "forgetting is rapid at first and then levels off"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following would be a part of your declarative memory system?",
          options: [
            "being able to name a hybrid car",
            "knowing how to react to a red light",
            "knowing how to drive a car",
            "knowing how to ride a bicycle"
          ],
          answer: "being able to name a hybrid car"
        },
        {
          question: "A schema for a routine event, such as going to the dentist, is called a:",
          options: ["script", "category", "exemplar", "prototype"],
          answer: "script"
        },
        {
          question: "Information such as the name of the person who sat in front of you in the fifth grade is stored in:",
          options: [
            "sensory memory",
            "short-term memory",
            "working memory",
            "long-term memory"
          ],
          answer: "long-term memory"
        },
        {
          question: "The term “anterograde amnesia” refers to:",
          options: [
            "the loss of the ability to form new memories.",
            "the loss of the ability to recall old events.",
            "the loss of short-term memory.",
            "the loss of all memory ability."
          ],
          answer: "the loss of the ability to form new memories."
        },
        {
          question: "The term “retrograde amnesia” refers to:",
          options: [
            "the loss of the ability to form new memories.",
            "the loss of the ability to recall old events.",
            "the loss of short-term memory.",
            "the loss of sensory memory."
          ],
          answer: "the loss of the ability to recall old events."
        },
        {
          question: "When we cannot retrieve information from memory, we say that _____ has occurred.",
          options: ["forgetting", "a memory trace", "sensory decay", "encoding failure"],
          answer: "forgetting"
        },
        {
          question: "The results of the Brown–Peterson short-term memory task can be explained by:",
          options: ["decay", "interference", "both decay and interference", "neither decay nor interference"],
          answer: "both decay and interference"
        },
        {
          question: "The calling to mind of previously stored information is known as",
          options: ["retrieval", "encoding", "storage", "forgetting"],
          answer: "retrieval"
        },
        {
          question: "You have just listened to a list of 20 words. When asked to recall these words in any order, you are LEAST LIKELY to recall the",
          options: ["first word", "second word", "10th word", "20th word"],
          answer: "10th word"
        }
    ],
    "week-6": [
      {
        question: "According to the notion of cognitive economy, a characteristic like “has wings” would be stored along with which of the following semantic memory nodes?",
        options: [
          "bird",
          "ostrich",
          "robin",
          "all of these"
        ],
        answer: "bird"
      },
      {
        question: "Contrary to the predictions of hierarchical models, Rips, Shoben, and Smith have found that people can verify the statement “A pig is an animal”:",
        options: [
          "faster than “A pig is a mammal.”",
          "faster than “A dog is an animal.”",
          "faster than “A pig is actually very clean.”",
          "faster than “A pig is a bird.”"
        ],
        answer: "faster than “A pig is a mammal.”"
      },
      {
        question: "According to research by Collins and Quillian, the statement “Siamese cats have blue eyes” will be verified:",
        options: [
          "slower than “Siamese cats give birth to live young.”",
          "faster than “Siamese cats give birth to live young.”",
          "in the same amount of time as “Siamese cats give birth to live young.”",
          "slower than “Siamese cats have tails.”"
        ],
        answer: "faster than “Siamese cats give birth to live young.”"
      },
      {
        question: "Collins and Loftus’s spreading activation theory differs from the hierarchical network theory in that:",
        options: [
          "it dispenses with the idea of cognitive economy.",
          "it relies on the assumption of hierarchical structure.",
          "it cannot account for the typicality effect.",
          "it makes stronger predictions than hierarchical models."
        ],
        answer: "it dispenses with the idea of cognitive economy."
      },
      {
        question: "ACT models distinguish among three types of memory systems:",
        options: [
          "working memory, episodic memory, and declarative memory",
          "semantic memory, episodic memory, and procedural memory",
          "procedural memory, declarative memory, and semantic memory",
          "working memory, declarative memory, and procedural memory"
        ],
        answer: "working memory, declarative memory, and procedural memory"
      },
      {
        question: "According to ACT models, _______ memory represents information in if–then production rules.",
        options: [
          "working",
          "procedural",
          "episodic",
          "semantic"
        ],
        answer: "procedural"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following would be a part of your declarative memory system?",
        options: [
          "being able to name a hybrid car",
          "knowing how to react to a red light",
          "knowing how to drive a car",
          "knowing how to ride a bicycle"
        ],
        answer: "being able to name a hybrid car"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is FALSE regarding a connectionist training “epoch”?",
        options: [
          "It begins by generating a random output.",
          "Connection weights are initially set at random levels.",
          "Generated output patterns are compared with target patterns.",
          "Back propagation occurs over many trials."
        ],
        answer: "It begins by generating a random output."
      },
      {
        question: "Studies of semantic memory have shown that in a lexical decision task, people are faster at responding to the stimulus “bread” if it is paired with a stimulus such as:",
        options: [
          "rencle",
          "dog",
          "xqkrf",
          "butter"
        ],
        answer: "butter"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following would be a part of your procedural memory system?",
        options: [
          "knowing that the Baseball Hall of Fame is in Cooperstown, New York",
          "knowing the lifetime batting average of Ted Williams",
          "knowing how to swing a baseball bat",
          "being able to remember the ball and strike count of the current pitch"
        ],
        answer: "knowing how to swing a baseball bat"
      }],
    "week-7": [
        {
          question: "A ________ is a mental representation of some object, event, or pattern.",
          options: [
            "category",
            "concept",
            "script",
            "memory"
          ],
          answer: "concept"
        },
        {
          question: "“Characteristic features” and “family resemblance” are important aspects of the _________ view of concepts.",
          options: [
            "classical",
            "prototype",
            "exemplar",
            "schema"
          ],
          answer: "prototype"
        },
        {
          question: "If “soda” is a basic-level category, then ______ would be a subordinate level.",
          options: [
            "soft drink",
            "beverage",
            "drink",
            "Coca-Cola"
          ],
          answer: "Coca-Cola"
        },
        {
          question: "According to the ______ view of concepts, people categorize new instances by comparing them to representations of previously stored instances.",
          options: [
            "classical",
            "prototype",
            "exemplar",
            "schema"
          ],
          answer: "exemplar"
        },
        {
          question: "The _____ view of concepts argues that concepts include representations of at least some individual instances and not only abstract summaries.",
          options: [
            "classical",
            "prototype",
            "schemata",
            "both exemplar and schemata"
          ],
          answer: "both exemplar and schemata"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is true regarding schemata?",
          options: [
            "A schema refers to something smaller and more specific than a concept.",
            "Schemata are passive rather than active.",
            "A schema contains only fixed parts, never variables.",
            "Schemata can indicate relationships among various pieces of information."
          ],
          answer: "Schemata can indicate relationships among various pieces of information."
        },
        {
          question: "The ______ view of concepts argues that a person uses his/her theories about the way the world works to justify the classification of instances in the same category.",
          options: [
            "prototype",
            "exemplar",
            "schema",
            "knowledge-based"
          ],
          answer: "knowledge-based"
        },
        {
          question: "The schema view of concept formation assumes that:",
          options: [
            "there are clear boundaries among individual schemata.",
            "there is cognitive economy among concepts.",
            "information is abstracted across instances.",
            "no information is stored about actual instances."
          ],
          answer: "information is abstracted across instances."
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is a good example of a basic level of categorization?",
          options: [
            "musical instrument",
            "piano",
            "electronic keyboard",
            "grand piano"
          ],
          answer: "piano"
        },
        {
          question: "If “sandwich” is a basic-level category, then ______ would be a superordinate level.",
          options: [
            "soup",
            "sub",
            "panini",
            "food"
          ],
          answer: "food"
    }],
    "week-8": [
        {
          question: "Several mnemonic devices, including the method of loci, the pegword method, and the method of interacting images, have in common their reliance on:",
          options: [
            "verbal rehearsal",
            "creating a story",
            "visual imagery",
            "connecting new information to well-known information"
          ],
          answer: "visual imagery"
        },
        {
          question: "According to the dual-coding hypothesis, which of the following word pairs would be easiest to remember?",
          options: [
            "fire-inspiration",
            "ferret-catalog",
            "freedom-honesty",
            "cat-liberty"
          ],
          answer: "ferret-catalog"
        },
        {
          question: "In Paivio’s study of paired-associate learning, subjects learned four types of word pairs: I. concrete-concrete (for example, book-table) II. concrete-abstract (for example, book-freedom) III. abstract-concrete (for example, freedom-table) IV. abstract-abstract (for example, freedom-honesty) Which of the following accurately portrays participants’ recall of the four types of pairs, from highest recall to lowest?",
          options: [
            "I, III, II, IV",
            "I, II, III, IV",
            "II, III, I, IV",
            "IV, III, II, I"
          ],
          answer: "I, II, III, IV"
        },
        {
          question: "The relational-organizational hypothesis is supported by:",
          options: [
            "the effectiveness of the method of loci.",
            "the fact that concrete words are recalled better than abstract words.",
            "the fact that noninteractive images do not facilitate recall whereas interactive images do facilitate recall.",
            "the effectiveness of the pegword method."
          ],
          answer: "the fact that noninteractive images do not facilitate recall whereas interactive images do facilitate recall."
        },
        {
          question: "Some theorists believe that there is a single code for all types of information; this code is known as a _______ representation.",
          options: [
            "visual",
            "pictorial",
            "verbal",
            "propositional"
          ],
          answer: "propositional"
        },
        {
          question: "Behaviorists objected to the study of visual imagery because:",
          options: [
            "it cannot be investigated with sufficient scientific control.",
            "there are too many individual differences in people’s abilities to visualize.",
            "behaviorists prefer to study animals and animals have no imagery abilities.",
            "we can only study visual imagery and not auditory images, olfactory images, etc."
          ],
          answer: "it cannot be investigated with sufficient scientific control."
        },
        {
          question: "Kosslyn compared people’s verification times for statements like “Cats have claws” (high association, small visual part of a cat) to “Cats have heads” (low association, large visual part of a cat). He found that people were:",
          options: [
            "faster at verifying “claws” whether or not they used visual imagery.",
            "faster at verifying “heads” whether or not they used visual imagery.",
            "faster at verifying “heads” when they used imagery, “claws” when they did not.",
            "faster at verifying “claws” when they used imagery, “heads” when they did not."
          ],
          answer: "faster at verifying “heads” when they used imagery, “claws” when they did not."
        },
        {
          question: "Finke’s principle of _____ states that mental imagery allows us to retrieve information that was not intentionally stored.",
          options: [
            "perceptual equivalence",
            "transformational equivalence",
            "implicit encoding",
            "structural encoding"
          ],
          answer: "implicit encoding"
        },
        {
          question: "Your mental map of your campus is probably:",
          options: [
            "larger than reality.",
            "smaller than reality.",
            "more regular, with more straight lines and right angles, than reality.",
            "less regular, with fewer straight lines and right angles, than reality."
          ],
          answer: "more regular, with more straight lines and right angles, than reality."
        },
        {
          question: "Cooper’s studies of the mental rotation of complex polygons indicated that:",
          options: [
            "people rotated more complex polygons in the same amount of time as simpler polygons.",
            "people took longer to rotate more complex polygons.",
            "people actually took less time to rotate more complex polygons.",
            "people were unable to mentally rotate a polygon with greater than 10 points with more than chance accuracy."
          ],
          answer: "people rotated more complex polygons in the same amount of time as simpler polygons."
        }
      ],
    "week-9": [
        {
          question: "Which of the following is/are generally agreed upon as necessary criteria/criterion for claiming that a communication system is a language?",
          options: [
            "regularity",
            "productivity",
            "referentiality",
            "both regularity and productivity"
          ],
          answer: "both regularity and productivity"
        },
        {
          question: "Bird songs and bee dances are not considered to be languages because:",
          options: [
            "they do not use words.",
            "they do not have a formal grammar.",
            "they cannot express infinite combinations of ideas.",
            "they do not have a permanent (written) form."
          ],
          answer: "they cannot express infinite combinations of ideas."
        },
        {
          question: "The smallest unit of language that carries a consistent meaning is called a:",
          options: [
            "feature",
            "phoneme",
            "phonetic",
            "morpheme"
          ],
          answer: "morpheme"
        },
        {
          question: "English speakers hear a distinction between “l” and “r” sounds; speakers of some Chinese dialects do not hear this distinction. This example illustrates a difference in the ______ aspects of the two languages.",
          options: [
            "phonetic",
            "phonological",
            "semantic",
            "syntactic"
          ],
          answer: "phonetic"
        },
        {
          question: "Studies of sentence comprehension have shown all of the following EXCEPT:",
          options: [
            "Exact wording of a clause is preserved in memory while that clause is actively being processed.",
            "After a sentence has been processed, exact wording is discarded and only the general meaning is preserved in memory.",
            "We typically do not consciously notice ambiguities in sentences.",
            "We do not process exact wording in memory; we only process meaning."
          ],
          answer: "We do not process exact wording in memory; we only process meaning."
        },
        {
          question: "What’s for dinner?” “Food.” The second speaker is breaking Grice’s maxim of",
          options: [
            "quantity",
            "quality",
            "relation",
            "manner"
          ],
          answer: "quantity"
        },
        {
          question: "Fodor’s modularity hypothesis proposes that:",
          options: [
            "language processing actually encompasses several subskills (modules).",
            "in understanding language, we separate sentences and phrases into individual units known as modules.",
            "thought processes are dependent upon the language we use to think.",
            "certain language processes operate independently of other cognitive processes such as memory and attention."
          ],
          answer: "certain language processes operate independently of other cognitive processes such as memory and attention."
        },
        {
          question: "Whorf’s linguistic relativity hypothesis:",
          options: [
            "asserts that thought is dependent upon language.",
            "is supported by studies of color perception.",
            "asserts that thought is dependent upon language, and is supported by studies of color perception.",
            "asserts that thought is dependent upon language, and is not supported by studies of color perception."
          ],
          answer: "asserts that thought is dependent upon language, and is not supported by studies of color perception."
        },
        {
          question: "Damage to Broca’s area often leads to:",
          options: [
            "expressive aphasia.",
            "receptive aphasia.",
            "inability to comprehend written language.",
            "both expressive aphasia and inability to comprehend written language."
          ],
          answer: "expressive aphasia."
        },
        {
          question: "The word “bat” is considered to be lexically ambiguous because it has two possible meanings.",
          options: [
            "True",
            "False"
          ],
          answer: "True"
        }
    
    ],
    "week-10": [{
      question: "A(n) _______ problem has a clear goal, a small set of starting information, and rules about how to attain the goal.",
      options: [
        "classic",
        "laboratory",
        "well-defined",
        "introspective"
      ],
      answer: "well-defined"
    },
    {
      question: "The problem-solving technique of ______ involves comparing the goal with the starting point, thinking of possible ways to overcome the distance between them, and choosing the best one.",
      options: [
        "generate-and-test",
        "means-end analysis",
        "reasoning by analogy",
        "mental set"
      ],
      answer: "means-end analysis"
    },
    {
      question: "The General Problem Solver (GPS) is a computer program that solves problems in crypt arithmetic and logic using:",
      options: [
        "means-end analysis.",
        "generate-and-test.",
        "reasoning by analogy.",
        "introspection."
      ],
      answer: "means-end analysis."
    },
    {
      question: "______ is a very important technique for solving the Towers of Hanoi problem.",
      options: [
        "Means-end analysis",
        "Generate-and-test",
        "Working backward",
        "Reasoning by analogy"
      ],
      answer: "Working backward"
    },
    {
      question: "A tendency to adopt a certain framework, strategy, or procedure, which can become an obstacle to successful problem solving, is called:",
      options: [
        "mental set.",
        "functional fixedness.",
        "well-defined thinking.",
        "ill-defined thinking."
      ],
      answer: "mental set."
    },
    {
      question: "The string problem often generates ______ when participants do not think to use the screwdriver as a pendulum.",
      options: [
        "functional fixedness",
        "mental set",
        "incomplete representations",
        "reasoning by analogy"
      ],
      answer: "functional fixedness"
    },
    {
      question: "________ involves appropriate novelty in generating solutions.",
      options: [
        "Intelligence",
        "Genius",
        "Creativity",
        "Mental disorder"
      ],
      answer: "Creativity"
    },
    {
      question: "Research on the incubation effect has shown that:",
      options: [
        "most empirical studies support the positive effects of incubation.",
        "incubation effects are only found with very long incubation intervals.",
        "incubation actually has a negative effect on performance.",
        "participants who take physical and mental breaks rarely show increased ability to solve problems."
      ],
      answer: "participants who take physical and mental breaks rarely show increased ability to solve problems."
    },
    {
      question: "The prefrontal cortex is involved in the ability to plan and solve problems.",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      answer: "True"
    },
    {
      question: "The detailed, concurrent, and nonjudgmental observation of the contents of your consciousness is called:",
      options: [
        "thinking.",
        "daydreaming.",
        "problem solving.",
        "introspection."
      ],
      answer: "introspection."
    }],
    "week-11": [{
      question: "Deductive reasoning involves which of the following?",
      options: [
        "going from general to specific statements",
        "conclusions that add new information to what is given",
        "going from specific to general statements",
        "going from specific to specific statements"
      ],
      answer: "going from general to specific statements"
    },
    {
      question: "When it is improbable (but not impossible) for an argument’s premises to be true and its conclusions false, the argument has:",
      options: [
        "deductive validity.",
        "deductive strength.",
        "inductive validity.",
        "inductive strength."
      ],
      answer: "deductive validity."
    },
    {
      question: "If a person has five letters in his or her name, then s/he is a Glirple. I can now validly assume that:",
      options: [
        "Shawn is a Glirple.",
        "anyone who is a Glirple must have five letters in his/her name.",
        "anyone who is not a Glirple cannot be named Susan.",
        "Shawn is a Glirple, and anyone who is not a Glirple cannot be named Susan."
      ],
      answer: "Shawn is a Glirple, and anyone who is not a Glirple cannot be named Susan."
    },
    {
      question: "In completing Wason’s four-card task, participants usually:",
      options: [
        "turn over the two cards that are necessary and sufficient to test the rule.",
        "turn over all four cards, when only two would have been sufficient.",
        "turn over all four cards, when only one would have been sufficient.",
        "show understanding of modus ponens but neglect modus tollens."
      ],
      answer: "show understanding of modus ponens but neglect modus tollens."
    },
    {
      question: "People have more difficulty working with:",
      options: [
        "quantifiers such as 'all' or 'no.'",
        "quantifiers such as 'some.'",
        "premises that have negatives in them, and quantifiers such as 'all' or 'no.'",
        "premises that have negatives in them, and quantifiers such as 'some.'"
      ],
      answer: "premises that have negatives in them, and quantifiers such as 'some.'"
    },
    {
      question: "The tendency to seek out information that supports our current beliefs is called:",
      options: [
        "a believability effect.",
        "a content effect.",
        "a confirmation bias.",
        "syllogistic reasoning."
      ],
      answer: "a confirmation bias."
    },
    {
      question: "The gambler’s fallacy is thought of as a special instance of:",
      options: [
        "framing.",
        "availability.",
        "belief in the law of small numbers.",
        "hindsight."
      ],
      answer: "belief in the law of small numbers."
    },
    {
      question: "Let p = 'Mary got an A on her exam' and q = 'John got a C on his exam.' In which of the following situations is the statement 'p & q' true?",
      options: [
        "Mary and John both got A’s.",
        "Mary and John both got C’s.",
        "Mary got an A and John got a C.",
        "Mary got a C and John got an A."
      ],
      answer: "Mary got an A and John got a C."
    },
    {
      question: "'All dogs chase cats. Bingo is a dog. Therefore, Bingo chases cats.' This is an example of deductive reasoning.",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      answer: "True"
    },
    {
      question: "The representativeness heuristic causes us to erroneously judge words with 'L' as their first letter to be more common than words with 'L' as their third letter.",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      answer: "False"
    }],
    "week-12": [
    {
      question: "_____ is a normative model for integrating different dimensions and goals of a complex decision.",
      options: [
        "Expected utility",
        "MAUT",
        "Framing",
        "Availability"
      ],
      answer: "MAUT"
    },
    {
      question: "Expert decision makers may rely on intuition and mental simulation, according to the _________ model.",
      options: [
        "recognition-primed decision-making",
        "MAUT",
        "EU",
        "elimination-by-aspects"
      ],
      answer: "recognition-primed decision-making"
    },
    {
      question: "Expected utility is a descriptive model of human decision making.",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      answer: "False"
    },
    {
      question: "When making a complex decision such as choosing 1 of 10 different apartments to rent,",
      options: [
        "participants spontaneously use multiattribute utility theory.",
        "participants use the same decision strategies regardless of the number of alternatives they are choosing between.",
        "participants systematically search for all available information.",
        "participants often eliminate some alternatives on the basis of only one or a few undesirable characteristics."
      ],
      answer: "participants often eliminate some alternatives on the basis of only one or a few undesirable characteristics."
    },
    {
      question: "Expected utility theory is usually regarded as a ________ model of decision making.",
      options: [
        "descriptive",
        "prescriptive",
        "normative",
        "both descriptive and prescriptive"
      ],
      answer: "normative"
    },
    {
      question: "You are offered a chance to buy a lottery ticket. The probability of winning is 1 in 100. If you win, the prize is $100,000. According to expected value, a 'fair' price for this lottery ticket would be:",
      options: [
        "$5.",
        "$10",
        "$100",
        "$1000"
      ],
      answer: "$1000"
    },
    {
      question: "Normative models of decision making describe:",
      options: [
        "ideal performance under ideal circumstances.",
        "what people actually do when they make decisions.",
        "cognitive illusions.",
        "hindsight biases."
      ],
      answer: "ideal performance under ideal circumstances."
    },
    {
      question: "You are a participant in an experiment in which you answer a long list of general knowledge questions. After answering each question, you are asked to rate your probability of being correct. If you are like the typical participant in such experiments, you will probably be correct on what percentage of questions for which you estimated '60% probability correct'?",
      options: [
        "55%",
        "60%",
        "70%",
        "100%"
      ],
      answer: "55%"
    },
    {
      question: "The normative model for integrating different dimensions of a complex decision is called MAUT.",
      options: [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      answer: "True"
    },
    {
      question: "You have just spent 10 minutes trying to figure out the answer to a single problem on your math quiz. In spite of your lack of success, you continue to struggle, neglecting to continue on to other problems because you’ve already invested so much time and effort in this problem. You have fallen victim to:",
      options: [
        "the sunk cost effect.",
        "a framing effect.",
        "the anchor effect.",
        "availability bias."
      ],
      answer: "the sunk cost effect."
    }]
  };
  export default questions;